  export const musica =  [
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "On%20which%20Beatles%20album%20would%20you%20find%20the%20song%20%27Eleanor%20Rigby%27%3F",
"correct_answer": "Revolver",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Help%21",
"Rubber%20Soul",
"Abbey%20Road"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20Elton%20John%20hit%20starts%20with%20the%20line%20%22When%20are%20you%20gonna%20come%20down%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Goodbye%20Yellow%20Brick%20Road",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Rocket%20Man",
"Bennie%20and%20the%20Jets",
"Crocodile%20Rock"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Who%20recorded%20the%201975%20album%20%27Captain%20Fantastic%20and%20the%20Brown%20Dirt%20Cowboy%27%3F",
"correct_answer": "Elton%20John",
"incorrect_answers": [
"John%20Denver",
"Billy%20Joel",
"Joe%20Cocker"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20was%20the%20last%20Aphex%20Twin%20album%20released%20before%20his%20decade-long%20hiatus%3F",
"correct_answer": "Drukqs",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Windowlicker",
"Syro",
"Collected%20Ambient%20Works%2085-92"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Who%20had%20a%201981%20hit%20with%20the%20song%20%22Japanese%20Boy%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Aneka",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Toyah",
"Sandra",
"Madonna"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20member%20of%20the%20English%20band%20%22The%20xx%22%20released%20their%20solo%20album%20%22In%20Colour%22%20in%202015%3F",
"correct_answer": "Jamie%20xx",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Romy%20Madley%20Croft",
"Oliver%20Sim",
"Baria%20Qureshi"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20song%20in%20rapper%20Kanye%20West%27s%20album%20%22The%20Life%20of%20Pablo%22%20features%20Rihanna%3F",
"correct_answer": "Famous",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Wolves",
"Ultralight%20Beam",
"Highlights"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20M83%20album%20is%20the%20song%20%22Midnight%20City%22%20featured%20in%3F",
"correct_answer": "Hurry%20Up%2C%20We%27re%20Dreaming",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Saturdays%20%3D%20Youth",
"Before%20the%20Dawn%20Heals%20Us",
"Junk"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "How%20many%20members%20are%20there%20in%20the%20idol%20group%20%22%C2%B5%27s%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "9",
"incorrect_answers": [
"48",
"6",
"3"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20artists%20did%20NOT%20remix%20the%20song%20%22Faded%22%20by%20Alan%20Walker%3F",
"correct_answer": "Skrillex",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Ti%C3%ABsto",
"Slushii",
"Dash%20Berlin"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%202016%20mixtape%20released%20by%20Venezuelan%20electronic%20producer%20Arca%3F",
"correct_answer": "Entra%C3%B1as",
"incorrect_answers": [
"%26%26%26%26%26%26",
"Sheep",
"Xen"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20British%20term%20for%20a%2064th%20note%3F",
"correct_answer": "Hemidemisemiquaver",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Semihemidemisemiquaver",
"Semiquaver",
"Demisemiquaver"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Who%20won%20the%201989%20Drum%20Corps%20International%20championships%3F",
"correct_answer": "Santa%20Clara%20Vanguard",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Blue%20Devils",
"The%20Academy",
"The%20Bluecoats"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20is%20NOT%20a%20song%20featured%20on%20the%20Lockjaw%20EP%20released%20in%202013%20by%20Flume%20%26%20Chet%20Faker%3F",
"correct_answer": "Left%20Alone",
"incorrect_answers": [
"What%20About%20Us",
"This%20Song%20Is%20Not%20About%20A%20Girl",
"Drop%20The%20Game"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20Death%20Grips%20album%20is%20the%20only%20one%20to%20feature%20a%20band%20member%3F",
"correct_answer": "No%20Love%20Deep%20Web",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Bottomless%20Pit",
"The%20Money%20Store",
"The%20Powers%20That%20B"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20is%20NOT%20a%20real%20song%20from%20the%20band%20Thousand%20Foot%20Krutch%3F",
"correct_answer": "Limitless%20Fury",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Let%20The%20Sparks%20Fly",
"Down",
"Give%20Up%20The%20Ghost"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20songs%20is%20not%20by%20Tatsuro%20Yamashita%3F",
"correct_answer": "Lucky%20Lady%20Feel%20So%20Good%20",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Merry-Go%20Round",
"Let%27s%20Dance%20Baby",
"Love%20Talkin%27"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20English%20title%20of%20the%20vaporwave%20track%20%22%E3%83%AA%E3%82%B5%E3%83%95%E3%83%A9%E3%83%B3%E3%82%AF420%20%2F%20%E7%8F%BE%E4%BB%A3%E3%81%AE%E3%82%B3%E3%83%B3%E3%83%94%E3%83%A5%E3%83%BC%22%20by%20Macintosh%20Plus%20%28Vektroid%29%3F",
"correct_answer": "Lisa%20Frank%20420%20%2F%20Modern%20Computing",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Smoke%20Weed%20420%20%2F%20Everyday",
"Make%20Your%20Move%20420%20%2F%20My%20Mind",
"It%27s%20All%20In%20Your%20Head%20420%20%2F%20Understand"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20year%20was%20Huun%20Huur%20Tu%27s%20album%20Altai%20Sayan%20Tandy-Uula%20released%3F%20",
"correct_answer": "2004",
"incorrect_answers": [
"1993",
"2006",
"2010"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20songs%20is%20NOT%20included%20in%20the%20Suicide%20Squad%20OST%3F",
"correct_answer": "Skies%20on%20Fire%20-%20AC%2FDC",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Heathens%20-%20Twenty%20One%20Pilots",
"Without%20Me%20-%20Eminem",
"Fortunate%20Son%20-%20Creedence%20Clearwater%20Revival"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "The%20key%20of%20sharps%20does%20the%20key%20of%20G%23%20minor%20contain%3F",
"correct_answer": "5",
"incorrect_answers": [
"3",
"7",
"0"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20year%20was%20the%20album%20%22Floral%20Shoppe%22%20by%20Macintosh%20Plus%20released%3F",
"correct_answer": "2011",
"incorrect_answers": [
"2014",
"2013",
"2012"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "In%20Kendrick%20Lamar%27s%202012%20album%2C%20%22Good%20Kid%2C%20M.A.A.D%20City%22%2C%20the%20album%27s%20story%20takes%20place%20in%20which%20city%3F",
"correct_answer": "Compton",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Detroit",
"New%20York",
"Baltimore"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Who%20designed%20the%20album%20cover%20for%20True%20Romance%2C%20an%20album%20by%20Estelle%3F",
"correct_answer": "Rebecca%20Sugar",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Matt%20Burnett",
"Ian%20Jones%20Quartey",
"Ben%20Leven"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20album%20was%20released%20by%20Kanye%20West%20in%202013%3F",
"correct_answer": "Yeezus",
"incorrect_answers": [
"My%20Beautiful%20Dark%20Twisted%20Fantasy",
"The%20Life%20of%20Pablo",
"Watch%20the%20Throne"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "%22All%20the%20Boys%22%20by%20Panic%21%20At%20the%20Disco%20was%20released%20as%20a%20bonus%20track%20on%20what%20album%3F",
"correct_answer": "Too%20Weird%20To%20Live%2C%20Too%20Rare%20To%20Die%21",
"incorrect_answers": [
"A%20Fever%20You%20Can%27t%20Sweat%20Out",
"Death%20Of%20A%20Bachelor",
"Vices%20%26%20Virtues"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20company%20did%20the%20animation%20for%20Peter%20Gabriel%27s%20Video%20Sledgehammer%20%281986%29%3F",
"correct_answer": "Aardman%20Animations",
"incorrect_answers": [
"HIT%20Entertainment",
"Illumination%20Entertainment",
"VIZ%20Media"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20first%20Studio%20Album%20to%20be%20released%20on%20the%20Internet%20with%20a%20%22Pay-What-You-Want%22%20price%3F",
"correct_answer": "In%20Rainbows",
"incorrect_answers": [
"The%20Help%20Album",
"Skrillex%20and%20Diplo%20Present%20Jack%20%C3%9C",
"Blackstar"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20of%20Michael%20Jackson%27s%20albums%20sold%20the%20most%20copies%3F",
"correct_answer": "Thriller",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Dangerous",
"Bad",
"Off%20the%20Wall"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "The%20heavy%20metal%20band%20Black%20Sabbath%20hail%20from%20which%20English%20city%3F",
"correct_answer": "Birmingham",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Manchester",
"London",
"Newcastle-Upon-Tyne"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Who%20is%20a%20pioneer%20of%20%22Minimal%20Music%22%20in%201960s%3F",
"correct_answer": "Steve%20Reich",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Wolfgang%20Amadeus%20Mozart",
"Brian%20Eno",
"Sigur%20R%C3%B3s"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20was%20the%20name%20of%20the%20hip%20hop%20group%20Kanye%20West%20was%20a%20member%20of%20in%20the%20late%2090s%3F",
"correct_answer": "The%20Go-Getters",
"incorrect_answers": [
"The%20Jumpers",
"The%20Kickstarters",
"The%20Beat-Busters"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20stage%20name%20of%20New%20Zealand%20singer%20Phillipa%20%22Pip%22%20Brown%3F",
"correct_answer": "Ladyhawke",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Lorde",
"Kesha",
"Anika%20Moa"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Pete%20Townshend%20collaborated%20with%20which%20famous%20guitarist%20for%20an%20event%20at%20Brixton%20Academy%20in%201985%3F",
"correct_answer": "David%20Gilmour",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Jimmy%20Page",
"Mark%20Knopfler",
"Eric%20Clapton"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Electronic%20artists%20Boys%20Noize%20and%20Skrillex%20have%20collaborated%20and%20released%20tracks%20under%20what%20name%3F",
"correct_answer": "Dog%20Blood",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Jack%20%C3%9C",
"What%20So%20Not",
"Noisia"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20lyric%20is%20about%20Red%20Hot%20Chili%20Peppers%20frontman%20Anthony%20Kiedis%3F",
"correct_answer": "%22A%20rainy%20Lithuanian%20%2F%20Is%20dancing%20as%20an%20Indian%22",
"incorrect_answers": [
"%22Fly%20away%20on%2C%20my%20zephyr%20%2F%20I%20feel%20it%20more%20than%20ever%22",
"%22And%20I%20liked%20the%20dimple%20in%20your%20chin%20%2F%20Your%20pale%20blue%20eyes%22",
"%22You%20used%20to%20be%20so%20warm%20and%20affectionate...but%20now%20you%27re%20quick%20to%20get%20into%20your%20regret%22"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20was%20the%20name%20of%20the%20cold-war%20singer%20who%20has%20a%20song%20in%20Grand%20Theft%20Auto%20IV%2C%20and%20a%20wall%20landmark%20in%20Moscow%20for%20his%20memorial%3F",
"correct_answer": "Viktor%20Tsoi",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Jimi%20Hendrix",
"Brian%20Jones",
"Vladimir%20Vysotsky"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Bj%C3%B6rk%27s%20%22Unison%22%20contains%20a%20sample%20of%20which%20Oval%20song%3F",
"correct_answer": "Aero%20Deck",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Textuell",
"Panorama",
"Do%20While"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20was%20the%20name%20of%20the%20rock%20band%20that%20Nobuo%20Uematsu%20formed%20that%20played%20songs%20from%20various%20Final%20Fantasy%20games%3F",
"correct_answer": "The%20Black%20Mages",
"incorrect_answers": [
"The%20Final%20Fantasies",
"The%20Espers",
"The%20Rock%20Summoners"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20first%20track%20on%20the%20Dave%20Matthews%20Band%20album%20%22Before%20These%20Crowded%20Streets%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Pantala%20Naga%20Pampa",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Stay%20%28Wasting%20Time%29",
"Rapunzel",
"Don%27t%20Drink%20The%20Water"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Chino%20Moreno%20is%20the%20lead%20singer%20of%20which%20alternative%20metal%20band%3F",
"correct_answer": "Deftones",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Tool",
"Korn",
"Type%20O%20Negative"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20official%20name%20of%20Prince%27s%20backing%20band%3F",
"correct_answer": "The%20Revolution",
"incorrect_answers": [
"The%20Paupers",
"The%20Wailers",
"The%20Heartbreakers"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Pamina%20and%20Papageno%20are%20characters%20in%20what%20Mozart%20opera%3F",
"correct_answer": "The%20Magic%20Flute",
"incorrect_answers": [
"The%20Marriage%20of%20Figaro",
"The%20Impresario",
"The%20Goose%20of%20Cairo"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Artis%20Leon%20Ivey%20Jr.%20is%20better%20known%20as%20which%20rap%20artist%3F",
"correct_answer": "Coolio",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Dr%20Dre",
"Snoop%20Dogg",
"Ice%20T"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20song%20originally%20performed%20by%20The%20Bee%20Gees%20in%201978%20had%20a%20cover%20version%20by%20Steps%2020%20years%20later%3F",
"correct_answer": "Tragedy",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Night%20Fever",
"Stayin%27%20Alive",
"You%20Should%20Be%20Dancing"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "A%20Caixa%20Malacacheta%20is%20what%20kind%20of%20musical%20instrument%20which%20is%20commonly%20used%20in%20Latin%20American%20music%3F",
"correct_answer": "Snare%20Drum",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Cow%20Bell",
"Bass%20Drum",
"Maraca"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Where%20was%20Nicki%20Minaj%20born%3F",
"correct_answer": "Trinidad%20and%20Tobago",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Haiti",
"Saint%20Lucia",
"Grenada"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20artists%20did%20NOT%20feature%20in%20the%20fitfh%20studio%20album%20%22Humanz%22%20by%20British%20virtual%20band%20Gorillaz%3F",
"correct_answer": "Snoop%20Dogg",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Vince%20Staples",
"Pusha%20T",
"Danny%20Brown"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "When%20did%20the%20rapper%20Eazy-E%20die%3F",
"correct_answer": "March%2026%2C%201995",
"incorrect_answers": [
"July%2011%2C%201992",
"February%2014%2C%201993",
"October%2021%2C%201994"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20year%20did%20Dire%20Straits%27s%20Song%20%22Money%20for%20Nothing%22%20release%3F",
"correct_answer": "1985",
"incorrect_answers": [
"1973",
"1980",
"1991"
]
}
]